<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<translations>
	
	<!--
	Add another language by taking the tags, copy
	and paste them, the put the language tag name as
	the tag, example:
	<es>Español</es>
	<pt>Portugues</pt>
	
	Language tags: 
	http://www.w3schools.com/tags/ref_language_codes.asp
	-->
	
	<!-- All pages -->
    <translation id="navbar-title">
		<en>Tessellation Renderer</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="navbar-subtitle">
		<en>Making PE Rendering Easy</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="navbar-toggle">
		<en>Tessellation</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="nav-link-home">
		<en>Home</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="nav-link-learn">
		<en>Learn How</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="nav-link-renderer">
		<en>Renderer</en>
	</translation>
	
	<!-- index.html -->
	<translation id="index-jumbotron-title">
		<en>Learn How</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="index-jumbotron-subtitle">
		<en>Learn How to use Tessellation to Make MCPE Block Models</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="index-jumbotron-text">
		<en>Make block models for Tessellation Mod, Your own mod, or just for fun!</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="index-jumbotron-learn">
		<en>Learn How</en>
	</translation>
	
	<translation id="index-jumbotron-renderer">
		<en>Renderer</en>
	</translation>
	
	<!-- learnhow.html -->
	<translation id="learn-title">
		<en>Beggining</en>
	</translation>

	<translation id="learn-subtitle">
		<en>Learn basics of Tessellations</en>
	</translation>

	<translation id="learn-renderer">
		<en>Renderer</en>
	</translation>

	<translation id="learn-home">
		<en>Home</en>
	</translation>

	<translation id="learn-text">
		<en>
			<tab/>Tessellation starts at the bottom North-West corner of a block, These coordinates are represented by 0, 0, 0, The Minimum X, Y, and Z. 
			Tessellation ends at the top South-East corner of a block, These coordinates are represented by 1, 1, 1, The Maximum X, Y and Z. 
			Just to Clarify, yes you can go past 0 in the negitives, as well as farther than 1 in the positives. Now, in the renderer there are two 
			box options, Add Box, whose base coordinates are 0,0,0,16,16,16 and Add Bound, whose base coordinates are 0,0,0,1,1,1 There is no difference, they work the same, 
			Add Box is simplified so you wont have think about decimals, its divided up so you can say, 0 - 1 is 1 minecraft pixel (Pixel on a 16x Texture). 
			Add Bound is for those who for some reason loke doings the hard way, I added it because of a complaint. 1 minecraft pixel in this is 0.0625 (1/16).

			<br/>Now that we went over Add Box and Add Bounds, lets talk about a simple render, like a slab.
			A Slab in Minecraft is half a block, so 1 block is 16 Minecraft Pixels tall (Y), Wide (Z), and Long (X). So, a slab is 8 Minecraft Pixels Tall, 16 Wide, and 16 Long.
			To make this lets start with the minimum values, of a default block is 0,0,0 - which is what we will use here.
			To make the maximum values, the default block is 16,16,16, we need it to be half of this height (Y) which will look like this 16,8,16. 
			Lets put it together and add a box with these coords 0,0,0,16,8,16. 

			<br/>Now that basics are down just experiment around and you will be making some amazing renders in no time!
		</en>
	</translation>
	
	<!-- All this wont be read, but This is the renderer text -->
	<translation id="renderer">
		<en>
			
		</en>
	</translation>
	
</translations>
